It's time to get started, Upgami, and this time I'm joined by Tayo Eguchi of Beyonce Subway and
and Minami Okamura of Beyons Amegami Kawai.
This is a program that goes behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's go behind the scenes with our two MCs!
I, Eguchi, have recently started cooking for myself.
I've always liked to cook.
But lately, I don't have the opportunity to cook for myself as much as I used to.
But when I think about the nutritional aspect, I thought it would be better to cook by myself.
I've started to think that it would be better to cook by myself from a nutritional standpoint.
I can't really invent or come up with my own recipes.
I usually watch videos of people who are good at cooking.
I usually watch videos of people who are good at cooking and copy what I think looks good.
Among them, the hamburger steak turned out to be very delicious.
It's amazing!
In her recipe, it's a Japanese style hamburger steak.
Absolutely delicious!
The sauce is really good.
So the hamburger steak was the best I've ever made.
I would like to make it again!
Wow!
I'd love to see some pictures on your blog or something.
I've never taken pictures at all.
I'm thinking of decorating it nicely and posting it on my blog.
I'm looking forward to it!
Yes, I am Okamura.
I'm doing an aori at the Hello Project concert in winter.
I'm doing an aori at the winter Hello Project concert I'm going to.
I'm trying to speak in the dialects of the various regions.
Oh, aori?
That's right.
At first, I was speaking in standard Japanese.
But I thought it would be fun if I could arrange it a little bit for each show.
I thought it would be fun if I could arrange it a little bit in each dialect.
I'm trying to do it.
When I went to Fukuoka Park
When I went to Fukuoka Park, I imagined the dialect of Fukuoka.
I had an image of something cute, so I thought it would be fun to make it more vocal.
I tried to encourage him to speak more and more, but he was too gentle.
I tried to encourage them to speak more, but they were too gentle.
The audience couldn't speak at all.
I wanted to make it more exciting.
But my voice became quieter than the first time.
It was a little awkward.
After the show, I heard a message from Eriana Ikuta from Fukuoka.
Rina Ikuta, who is from Fukuoka
came to the dressing room and said, "I'm sorry.
She said, "It's a little hard to get the audience excited if you do a stolt.
She told me that it would be better to say, "You can speak up more!
She taught me the dialect.
So, we tried it for the second show.
I was able to hear everyone's voice.
I was watching you.
I was watching that part.
But I think it's fun for the audience to hear the dialects of the different regions of the country.
I think it's a lot of fun.
and the fact that the members are teaching in their hometowns
It's very unique and very nice.
I was happy to have a chance to interact with them.
Now then, let's take a look at the latest uploads!
First of all, let's start from here!
Yuki Hirayama's hair arrangement
This is Yuki Hirayama of Angulum.
This time she's practicing the raised hair style she does at live performances.
Let's take a look.
Hi, I'm Yuki Hirayama from Angulum.
Today, I'm going to show you the hair arrangement that I've been doing at live shows since I cut my hair short.
I'm going to start today.
I'm going to start with the layers in this haircut.
The length here is the overall length, but about 2 cm from the parting is shorter.
I'd like to make this look good and have the hair naturally sozzled underneath.
I can't do it all at once because it's too short or there's too much hair.
I can't do it all at once, so I just put the top part of my hair up for now.
I'd like to put the top part of my hair up.
Okay, let's do the sozahane.
I'd like to go ahead and do it.
If you don't separate the hair, it will take a long time to grow out because short hair is short.
If you damage it once, it will take a long time to grow back, so I try to do it a little at a time.
It should be more like this, maybe a little lower than the sootherhane.
Do it a little bit more.
Otherwise, it will look like a lot of wieners.
I've finished the first stage of sozahane.
I'd like to work on the short hairs on the top.
I'm going to do the short hairs here, too, but I'm going to make them a little more wavy.
I'm going to start by curling the hair inwards.
If it's too sudden, it looks like it's broken, so I'm always careful about that.
It's a little too abrupt.
When I'm satisfied that I've achieved this kind of look, I'll do the bangs.
Make sure it doesn't rub off.
Then I'll do this side first.
I'm going to take the hair in this triangle shape.
The parting and the triangle.
It's a little bit long and thin.
A pin.
It's like a pin, but it doesn't have a clasp.
or something that doesn't have a clasp to hold it in place.
I'm going to pin it.
And then you just put it straight back in.
And then we'll just let it cool for a little bit.
Here's the parting line and here's the parting line.
It's really less than an inch.
It's just a little bit off, right?
I'm going to turn the temperature down a little bit.
I just turned it down to 140 degrees.
But I'm gonna do it now.
I'm going to hold it vertically, and I'm going to lift it up vertically.
And then, "Kkk," hold it like this, and then...
I'm going to ask you to stand up, so I'm going to pull the pin and stop it.
It's definitely not much.
It's really standing up, isn't it?
If it doesn't stand up like this, I can hold it down.
It's hard to get it up, so I'm going to do it again with the same movement, but a little looser.
I'm going to flow it this way.
Only this side is to be lifted up.
This side.
Stretch it out.
Then, here is the part where the curling method is different and it becomes a border.
I'm going to roll it up like this to add more air.
Loose
Almost straight.
It's not that big.
The big one is on top
And the big one is the bottom.
It's not the same as the shape I've been growing.
I took just the top.
Just a little bit more.
From the base here, like this.
And a little bit more on the outside here.
I had it cut like a wolf, so I went with that.
Now, these hairs tend to stand out and come back after a while, so I put some mascara on them to control them.
So I used a kind of mascara to control the stupid hairs.
I'm going to use a mascara like hair mascara to control the stupid hairs.
Once it's under control...
And then we want to make it stand up, so we're going to start today on this side of the forehead like this.
It's like a wax, so it will harden a little bit.
It's like wax, so it hardens a little bit.
I'm going to put hair oil all over.
I'm going to put it all over.
I like it a little heavier than smooth.
I don't like to put too much on the surface.
So I'm going to put it around my eyes from the back.
I'm going to apply it to the hair that you said is short.
Normally I don't put any oil on this.
I usually don't put oil on it, but for live performances, I put a little bit of oil under the bun.
Now I'd like to decide on the shape.
Here.
I'm going to go barefoot like this.
To the knot.
That's a little too much adjustment.
Then don't bother the cat.
Go cut off his butt.
Wow.
I'm not talking about people who cut their hair short.
Or short bob, or short bob, or short bob, or short bob, or short bob.
You want to keep it down?
I'm sure there are.
In that case, I'm short here.
I braid here.
I braid it.
It's pretty even if you can see it.
Do you think I can see it like this?
It'll be too tight.
Don't knit it so tight.
If you knit it...
If you knit it too tight
If you knit it too tight, the braid will be too peaked.
It will come out.
I made the braids on the outside.
So if you do it this way
It's cleaner than before.
It's personal.
Personally
I feel lighter.
I don't feel so rushed.
I'm not rushing around.
I only knit this one.
Sometimes I only knit both.
I did two strands, the other day I did two strands.
I left a little bit of hair like this.
I'm going to leave a little bit of hair like this, and I'm going to leave a little bit of hair like this.
Yes, that's it.
Like this.
Here we go.
I'm going to curl the hair here.
So that there's no white space.
Cover your forehead.
Start from the inside.
Now, close your eyes.
Curl here.
And then we'll do the waves.
Like this.
Turtle lä
Ending.
Like this?
Really, just a little bit.
Yes, my hair is done.
I guess it's straight like before.
I always curl my bangs like this,
I did that.
The point of this haircut is that I have done a lot of research on how to make bangs,
Now it's a little bit more gradual,
The hair is now a little loose, but I think it's close to the parting,
The back side of the hair also has volume, but it becomes more voluminous when it is danced,
But when I dance, the volume comes out,
When I perform live, I iron the front part of the hair in a triangle shape,
I iron the inside of the hair, then bend it up and down in the front,
That's the point,
I also do this when I want to control the volume,
I have layers here,
Which way did I do it?
I did it this way,
I did it this way, but the braids are mixed in with the short hairs here,
People with long hair tie it here,
So, it helps to control the amount of hair and to prevent the face from being caught in the hair,
If you have long hair, you tie it up here so that it doesn't get in your face and you don't have hair in your face.
But if you braid your hair loosely and fasten it
By hiding the hair out of the braid
I think this is one of the key points.
I would be very grateful if you could take a look at it.
Thank you very much. This is Ayaki Hirayama from Angelem. Bye bye!
I saw Ayaki Hirayama's hair arrangement, but hers is short with no bangs and mine is long with bangs, so they are the exact opposite,
I have never arranged my hair before, so I thought it would be really difficult, but you did a great job with ironing and combing, and I was impressed by how beautifully you finished it.
I had never seen a short hair arrangement before, and although there are some in Beyoncé, this was the first time I had seen one properly and carefully,
I thought that short people must have their own problems with their hair spreading,
I thought that maybe they had their own problems with their short hair spreading out, but I could see that they were doing a lot of creative things.
I could see that she was trying to do a lot of different things,
I was very happy to know that Yuki-chan is always looking good with this kind of hair arrangement.
That's all for this article on Yuki Hirayama's hair arrangement.
Angsty! Life's Beautiful!
Now on SAIYO!
Subtitle & Subtitle Kyou
Thanks for all your hard work!
Next up is Tsubaki Factory's "Atashi Rhythm" vocal recording for their latest album "Atashi Rhythm" to be released on February 21st!
Let's start with the melody as usual.
Let's do it!
I like to dress a little more flamboyant than everyone else.
It's none of your business.
I...
I'll lower my voice a little to sound a little cooler
I'll stop you right there.
I'll stop you.
Don't worry about it!
It's all taken care of!
That's about as short as it gets.
It's fine that you like clothes that are a little more flashy than everyone else's
It's fine.
It's none of my business if you think I'm bossy like that.
I'm like...
Oh, it's perfect!
Let's go to B melody
Yes, sir.
It's none of your business.
It's none of your business. I'm not sure if I'm good enough for you.
I'm a prawn, I'm a guy who cares, but I can't take anyone's place.
I want to believe you.
I like the main idea, but I'd like to add some accents and flow.
The first line, "I'm fine," is a little mature, a little sexy.
I'm not sure if it's okay to say "I'm...
I don't know if it's okay.
I wonder if it's okay that it's me.
The first line is a little shorter than the first person's.
I'm going to start with the first person, and then I'm going to bring it out in a more and more crèche-like way.
But I can't take anyone's place.
It leads to "I want to believe in you.
I don't know...
I can't get used to it, it's a bit like shrugging from the bottom
I can't get used to it
I can't...
I'm not sure if that's a good idea.
It's none of your business. I'm not sure I'm good enough for you.
But I can't take anyone's place
What I want to believe in...
You don't seem to be cutting it much. It's like you can't get away with it.
Maybe a little more.
But I can't take anyone's place
It's a little too extreme, but it's going up.
Okay, let's just take the last line.
I wonder if I'm good enough for you.
But I can't take anyone's place.
I want to believe in you.
Eiyo, then, the last line
But I can't take anyone's place
I want to believe that this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, if I dance to the rhythm, I'll stand up for myself
I'm the only one, more than anyone else, I want to be recognized as a memory
Listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, I can't even stand by the beats or the side-steps
I'm going to be me, somehow, without hesitation
I want to imitate it, and I'll get to it later.
I'll get it later... this, this, this, this... this is my rhythm.
I'll add a little nuance if I'm dancing.
If you're dancing, you'll only have two places to go.
If I dance, I'll just pull out the ass.
Keep it light.
Next. It's just one time for me
I want to admit it more tightly than anyone else
Listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me
I can't stop beating myself up.
The words are becoming more and more like me
I'll make it echo a little
I want to believe that this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me
I've been dancing to the rhythm and I've been myself
It's the only time I'm me
I want to admit it more than anyone else
Listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me
The beat won't stop, even if I tell you
I feel like I can be me without hesitation
That's good... let's just go with that.
Let's go with this.
Let's go half-carming!
I want to believe that this is it, this is it, this is it, this is it, this is it, this is it, this is it, this is new.
I'm the one who sings
I'd rather give and admit it than anyone else
I can't stop the new beat I can't stop the new beat I can't stop the new beat
I'm going to do it. It's not easy, so I'm going to cherish it.
It's not easy, but I'm trying to make it count.
It's a little jerky, the way you're bouncing around.
I'd like it if you could bounce a little smarter, or a little smoother.
It would be nice if you could bounce it a little bit more.
I'd like it if you could bounce a little smarter or smoother.
I can't even take your place.
I want to believe that this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, and if I'm dancing to the rhythm, I'm the one who sings.
I want to admit it more than anyone else Listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me
I can't stop the beat, the words, it's not easy, I'm trying to make it count
That's how I'm getting to be me
Okay, okay.
Okay, we're done! Thank you very much!
Yes, Tsubaki Factory's music.
I had an image of Tsubakifactory as very graceful and quiet,
But recently I've been listening to a lot of up-tempo rhythms in their songs,
I have always loved that kind of music, and I have been listening to this song as well,
I always listened to this song, but when I watched the recording video like this,
I always loved this song by Mr. Tsubaki, and I've been listening to it, but looking at the recording video in detail, I thought the detailed division of the chorus sounded really difficult and hard,
But I really love the way you sing the chorus with a squeaky voice,
I was very happy to see the recording video and hear her singing a lot.
Yes, it was very easy to see the change from before the direction to after the direction,
I was amazed at how he could instantly take what he said and sing it,
I was also impressed by the way she was able to sing the up-tempo, slightly funky song right from the recording stage.
That's all for Tsubaki Factory, Atashirhythm, and Saori Onoda's vocal recording.
It's been a while! Thanks for watching!
Beyonds With Sayu Eguchi of Subway
Beyonds Upcoming, by Minami Okamura of Rainy Morikawa Productions.
Here's the next one!
Angulum Red Line Vocal Recording
From Angulum's latest single.
Red Line Goto Hana's vocal recording.
Is there anything else that you're not sure about?
Well, let's give it a try.
Let's start with Emel.
Yes, please.
Okay, four lines.
Let's change it up a bit and go to, uh, something.
I wonder if I'm allowed to be an idiot... while I'm trying to get here and there.
I'll be on the next bus. I want to go home.
I want to go home.
It's okay, it's okay. You can do it.
I don't know if I'm allowed to be an idiot.
I'll be on the next bus.
I want to go home.
I wonder if it's okay if I act like an idiot.
Yes!
Let's do it early.
Yes! Please!
I hope it's okay to be an idiot.
I'm trying to do something here and there.
Don't come back on the next bus.
I just want to go home.
Okay, okay, okay, I'm almost done, but I just have one question.
I don't know if it's okay.
I don't know if this is a good place to be right now, but I'm kind of connected, so I don't know if it's okay.
I don't know if it's okay... if I'm being an idiot.
Let's just go there. Okay.
preview of next event
The beginning of the event is 886.
Database
Yes!
I missed you.
Yes, yes, yes.
I've missed you so much.
I missed you. I really missed you.
I'm still working on the database.
I'm still searching for the database.
I'm not being honest and open-minded, unconscious precaution
Unconscious precautions
OK.
Yes, thank you
Unconscious prevention
OK
Yes, ma'am.
Now, the bure bar show
Yes, sir.
# I've got a problem I've been waiting for
Today's look that got me all fired up.
Yes!
(Unconsciously taking precautionary measures without being honest and excited)
Today's code that floated through the worries I was warming up to
Somehow the words just kind of drifted away
A little more firmly
Today's code that I've been warming up to and have been worrying about
Yes!
(Unable to speak frankly, unconsciously taking precautions)
I've been warming up today's coordinate
Yeah, okay.
Okay, okay. Or do you want to go with B number 2?
I'm going to rap!
Okay.
I've been so worried. I'm so excited.
I'm gonna say it for you, I'm gonna say it for you, I'm gonna say it for you.
I'm gonna say it's for you
I'm gonna say the rest, really,
I'm gonna say, "I'm gonna say, "I'm gonna say, "I'm gonna say, "I'm gonna say.
I'm gonna say, "I'm gonna say..." I'm gonna say, "I'm gonna say...
I'm gonna come in a little harder on that part, too.
Yes! Let's try one more time.
My hand... yes, please!
Let's sing the lyrics!
That's what I'm talking about!
Okay! Let's try the chorus then!
♪ Idle, idle, idle, idle
Idol Idol Idol Idol Idol Idol Idol Idol Idol Idol Idol Idol Idol Idol
Kou tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan
I do I do I do Love script
Cross the red line cross the red line cross the red line
I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do
I'm for you, I'm for you, I'm for you, I'm for you, I'm for you, I'm for you, I'm for you, I'm for you
I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do
I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do
The red line This kiss is proof that I'm ready
I do I do I do I'll only show you the red line
Let's just do this one tape of I do I do I do
Between the heads, when I do I do
I do I do I not evil
Yes, yes, yes, yes, OK.
OK OK, now that was good.
OK, now the second half.
The scars of love are the future of the game.
I do I do only to you.
Can I just do this?
Best line This kiss is proof of my preparedness. I do I do I'll show it only to you.
It's only the first love of the show.
Yes, I do.
I feel like I'm getting a little ahead of myself.
It's like I'm going in a little too fast.
Ride harder, okay?
Listen to the music.
Yes, please. Please do.
I guess that's all then. Yes.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you very much.
I saw Hana-chan Goto's recording,
The atmosphere when Hana-chan answered "Yes! and when she started to sing, the atmosphere was so different,
I was really surprised at the gap between the two. I had an impression of Hana-chan as a very cute girl,
I had an impression of Hana-chan as a very cute girl, so to see her singing so powerfully and coolly like this, I thought it was very wonderful.
I love Hana-chan's very honest vocalization, and I could feel it today as well,
I was also impressed that she was able to add so many nuances to the song, which is really amazing since it was her first single,
I'm looking forward to hearing more and more of Hana-chan's singing as her sense of rhythm and other skills improve.
That's all for now, this is the vocal recording of Hana Goto of Angulum Redline.
Please look forward to the next one!
Ocha no oma! First album Channel 1 is now on sale!
I'm always on your side.
Egutsuseeto! It's time for Minami Okamura to say goodbye! We've seen a lot of footage this time, but the one that left the biggest impression on me was the recording of Hana Goto's Red Line vocal performance.
I personally love this song, and I've seen a lot of live videos and music videos of it.
I love this song so much, and I've seen many live videos and music videos of Angelem singing about strong and cool women, and I really like Angelem's image.
I love Angulum's strong and cool female image, and I was very happy to see Hana-chan's vocal recording of this song because I thought it was a very good thing that I could see the activities of the junior members, including Hana-chan, in addition to the senior members.
I was impressed by Miyuki Hirai's hair arrangement.
I was so happy to see Miyuki's hair arrangement while she was explaining it to us.
UpCami takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UpFront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we will introduce you to the parts you don't normally get to see.
This time, UpCami is joined by Masato Eguchi of Beyond Subway.
Beyonds Rain Forest Kawakai's Minami Okamura. Good bye.
Next time on Upokami,
Morning Musume。 13 Lake Up Call Recording of Waking Up,
And,
Juice! Bourne Voyage: The Miracle of Sou no Kiseki (The Miracle of Sou) will be released.
Enjoy!
Please subscribe to our channel.